Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. Organizational History, 1955-1983; 2.63 Linear Feet in 6 manuscript boxes
  This series chronicles the events leading to the founding of DSA. It documents Michael Harrington's early years with the Young People's Socialist League and his later role as chair of the Socialist Party, USA (which changed its name to Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, or SP-DSF, around April 1972), through his resignation from the party and the formation of the Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) in 1973. Additionally, materials cover the early negotiations between DSOC and the New American Movement (NAM), their eventual merger, and the formation of the Democratic Socialists of America (1982) through notes, resolutions, meeting minutes, negotiating instructions, and the merger agreement. Materials also include notes and meeting minutes from the Coalition Caucus, the precursor to DSOC; correspondence (most of which is from Michael Harrington and Carl Shier, Regional Director of the United Auto Workers and co-founder of DSOC with Harrington); Socialist Party, USA/SP-DSF mailings, resolutions, publications (such as New America), press releases, and Harrington's resignation letter; correspondence, memos, a proposed constitution, and the publication Socialist Reporter (a special report on the founding of DSOC) from the early days of DSOC; and early versions of DSA's constitution and bylaws. Michael Harrington's early published and unpublished writing is included here since it reflects the directions and views eventually adopted by DSOC. Published writing includes American Power in the Twentieth Century (published by the League for Industrial Democracy, 1967), and various articles for The New York Times and New York Herald Tribune, among others. Uunpublished writing includes a speech on youth and the labor movement, delivered at the 22nd Annual Central Labor Union Conference at the University of Illinois (December 1971), and an article draft on Vietnam (August 1971).
  - Notes and Writing on the History of Democratic Socialists of America, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Young People's Socialist League, USA, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Published Writing, 1955-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Unpublished Writing, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Party, USA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Party, USA, January-August 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Party, USA, September-December 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Party, USA, circa 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Party, USA, January 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Party, USA, February 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Party, USA/Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, March-April 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, May-June 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, July-August 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA -- Resignation of Michael Harrington as Chair, September-October 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, November 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, December 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA, circa 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Party-Democratic Socialist Federation, USA/Social Democrats, USA, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Coalition Caucus, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Coalition Caucus, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC), April-May 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Resignation of Michael Harrington from Socialist Party, USA, June-July 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Proposed Constitution, August 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC), September 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Founding Convention, October 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC), November-December 1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC), circa 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Other Organizations -- Constitutions and Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Early Communication, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Meetings and Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 5-6, Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Negotiations, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7-8, Box 292, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Merger Convention and Unity Celebration, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- Constitution and Bylaws, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Series II. Governing Bodies, 1971-2006; 13.63 Linear Feet in 30 manuscript boxes and 2 flat boxes; 9 audiocassettes; 1 VHS; 3.57 Megabytes in 212 computer files
  This series contains materials related to the governing bodies of DSA; additionally, there are materials from the governing bodies of DSOC and NAM. These materials illustrate how the governing bodies have led, and continue to lead, the implementation of DSA's major goals, both political and organizational. These materials include meeting minutes and agendas, correspondence and memos, reports, and notes from the National Board and the National Executive Committee (NEC). From circa 1978-early 1990s, there was also a National Office Committee (NOC), which focused on financial matters and events, such as the Convention. The minutes, reports, and memos of the NOC also are included here. This series also consists of National Political Committee (NPC) materials, which later took over the role of the board of directors (members are elected every two years by the delegates to DSA's National Convention). Some recordings of meetings, on audio and videocassettes, also are included.
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- Constitutions and Amendments, 1973-1981 (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA)-- Constitutions, Bylaws, and Amendments, circa 1983-1999
    - Paper Documents, circa 1983-1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, 1995-1999; TW_TAM_105_ER_1
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Council, 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 4, Box 292, Folder 4-5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- National Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Board, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board and "After the Elections: What Next for the Left?" Conference, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board and "First Meeting of Defiance and Revolt Against George Bush's America," Los Angeles, November 10, 1988; cuid43165 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0241)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: 86 minutesin two parts
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5, Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board Outreach Meeting with Barbara Ehrenreich, Michael Harrington, et al., 1988; cuid43172 (Box 159, Vhs 105.0163)
    Duration: 106 minutes
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board Leadership School, June 12, 1992
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0242)
    - Audio Recording (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0243)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Board, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5, Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5-6, Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC) Meeting, June 2-3, 1984
    - Audio Recording -- Union and student organizing, Election endorsements, cuid43166 (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0102)
      Duration: 95 minutes
    - Audio Recording -- Election endorsements (continued), UAW, travel expenses, cuid43167 (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0103)
    - Audio Recording -- Supporting socialist organizing in America, political action programs, internal subsidies and fundraising, cuid43168 (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0111)
    - Audio Recording -- Internal issues and strategy shortcomings, cuid43169 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0238)
    - Audio Recording -- Recruitment and membership, fundraising, cuid43170 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0239)
      Duration: 92 minutes
    - Audio Recording -- Finance and development, cuid43171 (Box 164, Audiocassette 105.0240)
      Duration: 94 minutes
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3-4, Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2-4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Executive Committee (NEC), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5, Box 14, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1971 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1972 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1973 (Box 293, Folder 1-2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1974 (Box 293, Folder 3-4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1975 (Box 293, Folder 5, Box 294, Folder 1-4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1976 (Box 295, Folder 1-2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1976-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1977 (Box 295, Folder 3-4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1978 (Box 295, Folder 5, Box 296, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1979 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1980 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1981 (Box 296, Folder 4-5)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Expanded National Interim Committee (ENIC), 1975 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Expanded National Interim Committee (ENIC), 1976-1977 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Expanded National Interim Committee (ENIC), 1978 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Expanded National Interim Committee (ENIC), 1979 (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Steering Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Steering Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1988 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4-5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6, Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1992 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Interim Committee (NIC), 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- National Office Committee (NOC), circa 1978-1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Political Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Political Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 19, Folder 2, Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3-6)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7, Box 20, Folder 1-2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1994
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 21, Folder 4-5, Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_2
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1995
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 22, Folder 3-5, Box 23, Folder 1-3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_3
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1996
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 23, Folder 4, Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_4
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1997
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_5
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1998
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_6
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 1999; TW_TAM_105_ER_7
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 2000; TW_TAM_105_ER_8
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 2001
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_9
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 2002
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_10
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 2003
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_11
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 2004-2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) -- National Political Committee (NPC), 2009-2017 (Box 343, Folder 13)
- Series III. Committees and Commissions, 1971-2003; 9 Linear Feet in 20 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box; 535 kilobytes in 46 computer files
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series consists of materials created by NAM, DSOC, and DSA's various committees and commissions, both temporary and long-term, which reflect the wide range of issues deemed important by DSA members. These issues include feminism, socialism and religion, and anti-racism measures, among others. These materials contain meeting minutes, agendas, reports, correspondence, and conference programs. The most recent name of the particular commission or committee is utilized. Publications by these committees are included in Series VII. Publications.
  - Commission Chairs, circa 1982-1995
    - Lists, Correspondence, and Meeting Materials (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_16
  - Activist Committee, 1996-2003
    - Correspondence, Agenda, Minutes, and Reports (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_12
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the DSA Transitional Economic Program, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Administration and Development Committee, 1988-1997
    - Correspondence, Agendas, Meetings, and Reports (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_13
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Agenda Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Anti-Corporate Task Force, circa 1973 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Arrangements Committee, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Anti-Racism, Latino, African American Commissions, 1972-2003
    - NAM -- Anti-Racism Commission, 1972-1982 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1977-1994 (Box 27, Folder 9, Box 28, Folder 1-2)
    - Electronic Records, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_14
  - Budget Committee, 1982-1997
    - Correspondence, Agendas, and Reports (Box 28, Folder 3-5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_15
  - New American American Movement (NAM) -- Campus Commission, 1978 (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Caucus for a National Strategy, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Chapter Steering Committees, 1977-1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Class Study Commission, 1976 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Clerical Network, 1978-1981 (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Electoral Politics, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Committee to Elect Michael Harrington as Delegate to Democratic National Convention, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Communications Committee, 1996-2002
    - Correspondence, Agendas, Minutes, and Reports (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_17
  - Communitarian Caucus, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Constitution Committee, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Cultural Commission, 1976-1979 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Affairs Committee, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 9-13, Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 5, Box 31, Folder 1-5)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
  - Democratic Agenda, 1981-1983 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Economic Policy Draft Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 5, Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Economic Task Force, 1971-1973 (Box 298, Folder 3-4)
  - Education Committee, 1974-1994 (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Electoral Politics Network, 1977 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Communications Committee, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_18
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Energy Commission, 1977-1982 (Box 33, Folder 5, Box 298, Folder 6-8)
  - Environmental Commission, 1991-2003
    - Correspondence, Agendas, Minutes, and Reports (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_19
  - Feminist Commission, 1972-1976 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Feminist Commission, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 8, Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Commission, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Feminist Commission, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Feminist Commission, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Feminist Commission, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
  - Feminist Commission, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 1, Box 341)
  - Feminist Commission -- Midwestern Socialist-Feminist Conference -- Zillah Eisenstein and Holly Graff Session, November 6, 1983
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0091)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0092)
  - Feminist Commission, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
  - Feminist Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Feminist Commission, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Feminist Commission, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
  - Feminist Commission, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Feminist Commission, 1991-1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Feminist Commission, 1995; TW_TAM_105_ER_20
  - Feminist Commission, 2000; TW_TAM_105_ER_21
  - Feminist Commission, 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Feminist Commission, 2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_22
  - Foreign and Military Policy Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Global Justice Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Green Caucus, circa 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Health Commission, 1976 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Health Commission, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 5-6, Box 299, Folder 2)